If I could work in any other niche
or any other industry,
I truly think it would be
within real estate and property.
Not because the prices go up and up
and there's
lucrative amounts of money to be made in
it.
This place for brand, personal brand,
content hooks, is
massive. And in this video,
I'm going to go through why I think this
is one of the
most exciting niches to be a part of.
But better yet, all of the tips
and tricks and everything we're going to
talk about
here will apply to every business.
Now, first thing, I must admit,
don't know if you're the same as me,
every time I
go past a house, especially big ones,
I'm thinking, "What does it look like in
there?" If I drive through Virginia Water
in the UK, or you're going around
Beverly Hills,
you kind of just want to go knock on
people's doors and say, "What
do you do? How did you make your money?
And can I have a look around your house?"
I shit you not. Let me find them.
I even send these to my friends. Right,
here's one.
I don't know if you guys are like me,
but you send your mates properties and you
go, "If I win the lottery,
I won't tell everyone, but there will be
signs." Now, this one here.
This is what $2 million buys you on the
Sunshine Coast.
This is the best hook ever.
When people say, "This
is what this amount of money
buys you in this location." Because that's
what we're all wondering.
Whenever we go to buy a house, you think,
"What's the maximum amount I could save
for a deposit? Now,
what borrowing power does that give me?
What can I afford?" Then we have the
location in which we want to live in
or choose
to live in. So straight away,
we know what the video is about.
Within, what, three seconds?
We know we're looking at a property in the
Sunshine
Coast that's $2 million.
That's about £1 million.
And this has the potential to be the
coolest Airbnb I've ever seen.
This converted warehouse has a-
Converted warehouse.
Any of the dudes listening right now,
I don't know what it is.
There is something about men.
I've got a gym.
I've got a lovely big gym facility.
I'm in a loving relationship.
I've got a family. But as a man,
there's always part of you
that thinks you would
love to convert a warehouse
or even an industrial
space and turn it into the ultimate lad
pad.
Even now, I think,
"Let's get a TV up on the screen.
Let's turn this into a UFC Sundays place."
There's something about men that just
want to live in a mattress on the floor in
a massive room.
Ramp, basketball hoop, and
is a whopping 503 square meters in total.
Yeah.
Incredible.
You didn't see that,
but you did see this 385 bottle wine
cellar
that-
Don't even like wine.
Gives me the worst hangovers of my life,
but I'm listening,
brother
...
goes onto this Mediterranean living
and dining area.
Look at that. Look at the space.
You could swing a cat in there.
I'm already thinking about my life in this
place.
I'll be sat on the sofa
and shout to my missus,
"Tay." "What?" She's so far away,
she can't hear me.
And I don't know about you, but this
is the perfect place for a party.
With the beach only six minutes away,
you can already hear the dollar signs when
you get this up on Airbnb. Now-
Airbnb. See, selling yourself short here,
brother
...
if activities aren't really your thing,
follow me upstairs to-
Look at that staircase.
I'm already thinking about me going up
them stairs
...
find the perfect place to enjoy a book
or a little Netflix and chill alongside
this stunning Japanese limestone kitchen
and butler's pantry with curved-
Look at that table
... and heaps of storage. With all
that space downstairs,
you could park at least
10 car-
Look at that.
It's like an industrial warehouse.
It's an office.
No, it's a house
... If toys were your thing and-
Look at those beds
... these twin rooms
are what every kid dreams of.
The bathroom floor and walls
are finished with-
We're moving to Sunshine Coast
... micro cement
that continues with the European vibes of
the warehouse.
Now,
as we finish in this minimalist master
bedroom, would you pay $2 million for
this?
Finishing with another hook as well.
Would you pay 2 million? Yes.
Brilliant hook.
You got our inquisition. Now, even
if we live in Australia, even if we don't,
we
want to know. We want the payoff. This
is what $2 million buys you.
It's either going to be a good deal
or a bad deal,
and even the bad deals we want
to watch. Now, there's one here
that I wanted to show you as well,
which is
genius. "Where I would hide if I
was to play hide and seek in my new
listing."
Straight away we're establishing it.
Now,
one thing that I disagree with a lot of
other creators is some people like to
initiate a hook with a title.
This is my new listing, and this
is where I'd hide if I
were playing hide and seek
in own-
See, for me, I can't read the title
and listen to the hook at the same time,
so
there's a large part of me
that would rather just good captions,
middle of the
screen so I can listen along with what
you're saying.
The hook here was so good we didn't need
the title, but I disagree.
She got fucking 168,000 likes.
What the fuck do you know, James?
This home. Follow me. This
is the living room.
I bet you can't find me.
Again, brilliant. The whispering.
I love it.
I think you should look under the couch.
I'm right here.
Look at this-
Probably should've put
that dead cat on a little bit more.
What people hate is the ha, ha or the puh,
puh.
That's why some people call them, well,
you get pop filters, don't you?
Technically,
this on top of this Shure SM7B is a pop
filter. Now, for any of you wondering,
this one is supposed to
be one chakras away. Far out, brother.
Cowabunga, mate.
Caught a couple of rippers on Alfred,
mate.
But then if you have the Chris Williamson
pop filter, the bigger one, you're
supposed to be a fist away.
So closer to the mic,
more pop filter required.
Where's your microphone, James?
Don't worry about it.
Beautiful kitchen. I bet you're thinking,
"Is she in the cabinets?
Is she in the oven?" No,
I'm right here behind these fake flowers,
but they
sure are pretty.
Look at this beautiful bedroom.
See, look, I would say this
is less interesting than the other one,
but just the
ingenious nature of the hook,
you're making it fun.
But ultimately, at the end of the day,
she's out here trying to sell a property.
The best thing you can do
is get eyes on it.
Any property,
depending on how good a deal it is,
you're going to only need a
certain amount of people to know about it
for 10% of them to book an
inspection,
for fucking 30% of them to put an
offer. And the more offers,
the more it's going to go to.
One thing I do hate about Australia
is how they have this culture of going to
auction,
and not a lot of people talk about this.
The winner's curse.
What that is, in auctions, the winner
is cursed because the person who
wins the auction paid the most money.
So in essence,
whoever wins the auction loses on the day
because
out of all the people, you won,
but you kind of lost because you paid the
most.
Fantastic. Absolutely fantastic.
Today,
I'm showing you this four-bedroom detached
family home
tucked away in a very quiet position in
West End, South-
So straight away,
it's a little bit slower to the pace.
A little bit slower.
It's not bad by any means, but this
is what £785,000 could buy
you in Southampton. To me,
that straight away gives me so
much more. With hooks, with the setups,
with everything we do in the first part of
the content,
we want to establish what it
is about so they can make the decision of
whether they're in or out.
To famously quote, "Oi, you,
are you going to bang
though?" Like a lot of the times through
the process of wanting to fornicate with
someone,
you're better off not getting your wires
mixed and just finding out.
Are you interested? Yes or no?
Because better to give the people the
opportunity to
leave when they want to leave.
The property offers over 2,000 square foot
internal-
I'd argue that the music on this one's a
little bit too loud. This guy, amazing.
Okay,
so this one we have a visual hook Which
is I was about to count down
saying that there
was too long time gone without saying
anything by a good visual
up here.
Hi.
The question is posed, where is this?
Adam,
and I am today in the garden of the new
property that we are taking to the
market.
No offense, Adam, I don't care.
I want to know what's going on.
I want to know how much it is,
I want to know how many rooms there are,
and I want
to know how many bathrooms there are,
and I want to know what things are in the
property that are a bit interesting.
Does it have a dance floor in the
basement?
Does it have a little Fritzl cupboard?
And again, Adam
It's in a very exclusive area of Salisbury
You're chatting waffle, bruv
Green down its own private road.
It also affords this amazing view
behind me across the river
I'm gone,
brother. I'm gone. Now,
whilst we are doing this,
I actually need to show you guys
something.
This, for a long time,
was what I considered the OG house.
I was like, if we sell New Tonic
and if we were to make a bazillion pounds,
this was going to be the property.
I remember walking past this, pandemic,
going for a little jog, and I was like,
"This would be me.
I'll get my friends round." I could be
like, "Guys, what's it
like being poor?" "Oh, guys,
let's do the barbecue at mine.
Your houses are tiny.
What's yours got a view of?
A road?" So this is like the Bronte OG.
I'll probably come
and look at this property once every six
months, and then I
abuse myself. I go, "James, you're poor,
brother.
You're poor." Right now,
I can hear my neighbors. That's a problem.
But let me show you this, right? See,
even now, some of you are still here.
You're not even interested in me.
That's why I've not introduced who I am
or what I
do or what I sell in this video.
You just want to see inside people's
houses.
I think back in the day,
we want to look inside people's caves,
and I think there's
something exciting about walking around
someone else's house.
It's why we like going to look at property
listings.
I think it's deep ingrained into our DNA,
and if you deny those emotions, you're
lying to yourself. I warn you guys,
with what we're about to watch, your
life will never be the same.
I also won't lie to you,
I've got two members of staff
that I've taken on in the last six months.
One of them is 24, the other one is 21,
and I both sent them this listing
just so they can know,
if you keep working hard,
you'll never have that house,
but I will,
and I will let you come round
occasionally.
So I said, "You best be working hard,
boys." Does she come with the property?
Doubt it.
I wouldn't be interested personally.
I'm in a loving relationship,
you know that? Are you ready? This one
is better.
Better located. Right, not down on
that cheap block where the other one was.
Now I get it,
it's not the widest of establishments,
sure. But look at that.
You're looking at Bronte pool probably,
if not, the most sought-after pool
in the bloody world. Look at that.
One level, two levels, three levels, four
levels, five levels. Adam Sullivan, EBT,
if you don't buy this,
you're poor. Look at that pool.
And do you know what?
If I went past this, look at this guy,
this surfer down here.
He's looking at that house going,
"I wonder what it looks like inside." Just
like
every other alpha male you're walking past
going, "I would do anything to know
what that house looks like on the inside."
But don't worry, brother. Look at this.
Look at that for a garden. Beautiful.
Do my little workouts out there. Alfie.
Be my dog's new little place to go for a
pee. Is that grass real? You don't care.
Wow. Your biggest problem in this house
is which top floor do you go to?
Pilates room. Or is that a TV?
I don't even know.
Double car parking garage. Look at that.
Look at the natural light.
Oh, that's a bedroom.
Fucking hell.
Imagine out there with your fam. "How
was your day?
How were the kids?
Thanks for getting the kids from school."
We've all got
different motivational ways of keeping
ourselves going in life.
But me, occasionally,
really looking at some of the nicest
properties in the
world and coming to the conclusion
that I'm about 20 million short, brother.
Hear the kids having fun in the pool next
door.
That wouldn't be happening in this
property.
I'm not the biggest fan of the lottery,
but after looking at this, you're like,
"Let's scratch away, brother." My God.
All right. So where were we?
In the midst depression. This week,
I had quite a few real estate
agents join my business mentorship.
Link's in the description, don't worry.
And Josh here,
I've just been chatting to in the Discord,
and I was like, "Mate,
I'm so excited by this niche.
I'm turning this into a video." So we got
Josh
Meltz. Good job you're in America,
because in the UK,
calling someone a melt is
like a derogative like, "Oh,
you're a melt, bruv." Helping you buy
and sell in
San Diego. I love this as a title.
That's just great.
Exactly what it says on the tin. Realtor.
You're a realtor.
Explore the best of Rancho Santa Fe.
Free relocation guide at com.
So I feel like this bit here,
I'm not sure what that is,
but maybe we can get rid
of that. Free location guide. What
is a relocation guide?
Let's have a look at this.
Thinking of moving to North County San
Diego?
Get the ultimate insider guide.
I'd maybe change this.
Maybe like the inside scoop.
Maybe could we position this as a
locals guide?
Sometimes you feel like realtors
or estate agents are a little bit
snakey.
They're not really being truthful
or transparent because at the end of the
day, they need to make their cut.
So the best neighborhoods, local schools,
hidden gems. See, like even here,
expert tips.
Maybe even something like just
that hidden gems. I love that.
Could have this page have been something
along the lines of San Diego's hidden
gems. Give me your email address
and I will send you the gems seven days
before they go out to public.
Seven days before anyone else sees them.
They'll be in your inbox a week before
anyone else.
You will be the best informed,
the most informed.
You will know as much as every single real
estate agent.
Inside scoop, hidden gems. I like that.
Just when you say guide,
I feel like this could be the wrong use of
words.
You're doing a tour somewhere.
You're walking around.
"Fancy a guide?" "No, thanks."
But I like it.
I like that you're putting it out there.
I'd be interested to know how many people
are getting that.
Now, second thing,
I haven't even looked at your content yet,
but we should have
some kind of chatbot,
and I'm just going to show some of you
guys here who love a
chatbot.
Where quite simply you could say the
trigger is on Instagram,
comments on your post.
Now we can change this trigger to be all
posts and all reels. Any comment. Cool.
Let's just say.
So now, Josh,
any time anyone on your page comments
anything like, "Wow,
that's a nice property.
Wow." And let's just have a look at this
for a second. Where was that babe?
Where was that fit bird? Here she is.
This one here.
What are we looking at in the comments?
We're looking at comments for those.
7,564 comments. 7,000. Okay. If
she ain't got a chatbot set up, where
is she? Lisa, what are you saying?
Come join my mentorship.
Come give us your money.
Sorry,
I've had a few New Tonics this morning.
You get to this bit here, send message.
"Hey, it's Josh. Thanks for that.
What amazing property.
Just wanted to let you know, if you're
willing to give me your email address,
I can keep you
in the inner circle of Hidden Gems.
It's free, and I won't spam you.
All the best,
Josh. Cool. Then we go to add button,
Hidden Gems.
Maybe she even gets a little emoji.
Then we go open website,
www.joshisaboss.com/sandiegoguide.
Cool. You see what I'm saying? Cool.
Now, Josh,
you're now going to get incentivized for
every single piece of content
that you put out. Ba-bum.
The more it goes through the algorithm
and people watch,
which they will because they're interested
in, we all want to see the inside of
people's houses. The more that happens,
the more people are going to trickle
through your email system. Now,
when people get this email,
if they live in bloody
North Carolina or they live in flipping
Stavanger in
Norway,
they're not going to sign up because they
live in fucking Norway.
But the people that
are in the local vicinity are going to go,
"Do you know what?
You son of a bitch, I'm in." Of course,
there's just a little...
Let's delete that before people get sent
to Josh's iPhone. Cool.
So I've not looked at this profile before
I've got here.
Has a little look down there. Love that.
And do you know what?
I don't even know if we need this. You
are the brand.
Josh Meltzer is the brand.
We want people to be like, "You
need Josh Meltzer in your life." Okay.
My career journey.
I do like to make sure things aren't too
much about you because they're going to
find out, bro. When they get your emails,
and when they're talking to you about a
property, and you're like, "Hey, yo,
let me give you a call," and you're just
having fun,
and you feel like you're making friends
with people, they're going to
love you anyway.
If you get back to them in a timely
fashion, you care.
And if you want to win over people,
you can be like, "Hey,
this property's up for
3.2,
make an offer of three." I think they'll
take it.
That's how you become a legend with these
people.
List of best neighborhoods in caption.
Okay. Right.
This ain't it.
So if you want to tell me about this,
that's your hook.
What are the best neighborhoods to live in
in North County, California?
I don't know. Then there should be music,
and as the music is boom,
boom, boom, visuals.
Show me these areas at sunset.
Show me drone pans of the area.
Show me the properties that are in that
area.
Don't show me a bunch of dudes having a
beer.
Bit of a missed opportunity, but anyway,
you got 350 likes, so what the fuck do I
know? And ultimately,
I just don't like making people do the
work
reading that.
Five things I stopped worrying about since
I moved.
Baby, my heart don't break here. Love
means nothing.
See, here,
I think maybe we create almost some fake
beef.
Why West Coast is better than East Coast.
And again,
we're kind of getting all of the caption
to do the work here.
Show me a bit of personality.
Get in front of camera.
Be like, "This beach right here
is proof as why West Coast
is better than East
Coast.
I lived in the East Coast for 10 years,
but the reasons I love it here, the
sun's always out, the weather's perfect,
people are happier, more
opportunity, people
are more entrepreneurial.
If you're thinking of moving over here,
you should. And guess what, guys?
If you don't love it,
you can always move back to the East
Coast."
This sounds like an old memory.
Where are the properties, brother?
Where are the properties?
Now, who's the guy?
I actually can't remember his name,
so let's see if
ChatGPT. Jason Ballo. This is the guy,
Jason Ballo. Jason,
if you're watching this,
I follow you on TikTok, brother, all
right? Now, this guy is killing it.
Look at this, "Sydney wide buyer's agent.
Call or text." Just has his number.
Love that. Now look at these reels,
one million, four million, four million.
Every single video, I assure you,
is the same hook. Are you ready?
This is what $15.5 million buys you in
Sydney.
This is what $9.2 million buys you in
Sydney. Let's...
This is what 1,715,000 buys you in
Sydney.
This is what $1.5 million buys you in Sy-
Now listen, bro,
I ain't having a pop here.
This can probably go, and if you
are going to be doing that,
let's get a bit of a timepiece going on,
brother. Maybe a Rollie.
Look, a stainless Submariner,
not ever going to go wrong.
Just get a little stainless.
Fancy a little GMT,
maybe a little GMT with a
Jubilee. With your skin tone,
we can maybe even get
away with a two-tone. Maybe
Root Beer. And for any of you out there,
the solid gold Root Beer, the rose
gold one, too heavy. It
was my first Rolex, way too heavy.
With this complexion,
maybe even an AP Royal Oak Offshore.
What do I know? Hey,
stop getting distracted.
Let's check it out.
Now,
the one thing I want to draw attention to
here is Jason is a master of also
baiting people because property prices
are so incredibly
expensive and just crazy.
These properties are worth this amount.
So this one I've seen before.
This is what $9.2 million buys-
So $9.2 million.
Look at where he's decided to create the
visual hook
that goes along with that verbal hook.
You're like, "What?
Where's the $9 million, brother?"
... you in Sydney. Let's check it out.
The first place he shows. Again,
his first emotions
when coming to this property
were like, "How the hell
is this worth 9.2 million?"
As we enter the home here through the four
car-
Think about the emotions people
are facing right now at this point.
As they're getting to this point,
they're probably thinking, "9.2?
This is ridiculous."
And think of the emotions that
are pent up.
It's the government's fault.
Property's not affordable.
They're not building enough.
Lockup garage. This property
is located in Russell Lea,
which is eight kilometers from the CB-
Then they get here though
... the huge front lawn here. The property
sits on approximately 790-
796 square meters. And for any of you
that don't know, in Australia, it's crazy.
A lot of places people didn't want to live
100 years ago. Think about this.
In the UK, we have something similar.
Rory Sutherland made a good point about
this.
If you're doing really well in London,
and you can afford a house that's
£1.5 million in Fulham,
you're living in a house that probably a
postman used to live in. So you work hard,
you save up hundreds of thousands of
pounds for a deposit,
you move into a three-bed in Fulham.
That probably had a postman living in it
100 years ago, and even then it was
considered uncouth to have, "Oh,
your house, the
walls touch walls of other properties."
But because of just the state
of the world and how many people
are still alive and the lack of property,
suddenly
that is doing incredibly well. So again,
fucking few hundred years ago,
this might not have even been a
sought-after place.
Seven kilometers from the city,
far too far,
but now it's a very sought-after
place. Anyway.
Six square meters of land.
Off to the left-hand side here we have
a laundry and toilet. The house makeup
is a three bedroom,
one bath-
The reason this video would've done so
well Is even at this point,
we've been here
about 30 seconds,
we haven't actually seen enough of the
property to get any
tangible payoff. So we are retained.
So Instagram's probably got a fucking
gazillion reels in front of it
and it's gone,
this guy Jason has got a reel where 92% of
people-
Mm
... are still watching at 42 seconds,
therefore this reel must be of
absolute value.
Four car. Into the family room.
Adjoining kitchen.
'70s style kitchen. Sunken din-
We're about to get the payoff as well.
Remember in content, we have the hook,
we have the setup, then eventually we need
the payoff. And the payoff
is usually where people leave.
Now,
if Jason had started this reel in this
room we're about to go into, you
see how I'm leading you up to build
suspense for the payoff as well, people
would've seen it, understood it,
got the information they need, and left.
So whether or not Jason even knows this
or not, the way he's doing this is fucking
genius.
Living space into bedroom number one of
the property.
Still building. We want to know what
is down there where that light
is. Is it good? Is it bad?
Is this a rip-off, or is this a bargain?
Even if we're not potential buyers for
this, it's still genius.
We have bedroom number two.
Again, blue.
The only bathroom of the property.
The master suite facing east.
We have this living
space on offer here with all the views,
and guys, this-
Look at the size of this property.
It's massive
... what it's all about,
the east-facing backyard.
And that's what $9.2 million buys you in
Sydney.
Because ultimately,
he's probably not even selling the house,
he's selling the
development. Maybe they put flats there.
Maybe.
It's fucking great. Again,
in the eastern suburbs.
You know what I was saying before,
this was probably the house of a shoe
shiner.
Someone who fucking shined shoes for a
living, mate.
Maybe even eight years ago,
your grandad lived in this
property.
This is what, 1,715,000-
Your stamp duty on that alone is like 80K.
£40,000 just in stamp to the government
with money you've already paid tax on.
Cheers
... buys you in Sydney.
Let's check it out. Alrighty, legends.
This-
£800,000, guys. £800,000. If I
was a crackhead, I wouldn't
even shoot crack in there
... house is located in Glebe,
a suburb 3K sou-
This comment, "Is it already haunted
or do you have to pay extra?" Okay,
so getting
to the point,
some real estate agents have really
cottoned onto the fact that there
is, from a human psychology standpoint,
this massive ongoing thing where people
want to know more about property.
And although this goes against
niching,
Jason here wants to appeal to everyone
because everyone's interests are
in line with property, property value,
how much something is worth, what you get
for your money.
If four million people see it, the sheer
amount of millions of views, free views.
There are real estate agents out there
using paid ads, maybe doing some in-person
marketing.
This guy gets to cheat the system.
All he needs to do
is get permission to go to a property.
So if you're in the real estate market,
you need to get a professional microphone,
you need to get someone to hold a camera,
you need to visit as many properties as
you can,
and you just need to show people around
it.
And the thing is here, even
if Jason isn't the real estate agent
that sells any of
these,
he is building his personal brand
and business.
He's building his following.
These 54,000 people, 50,000 of them
probably aren't in the market to buy a
property. They're just interested.
This is the amazing thing.
Even think about my coaching business.
I've got 1.4 million followers,
but only like 10, 15,000 people are
using me as a coach in my coaching app,
and that's all right.
Because if I can make a video
that appeals to millions of people
and only a few
hundred clients come out of it,
that's fine. That's okay.
Property's always going to be selling.
People are always going to need homes.
Maslow's hierarchy of needs. This
is such an exciting place to get into,
and the thing that kind of kills me, Josh,
where are you?
Is I don't see this, and this
is what I want.
I want to see these properties, brother.
And look.
This is the best part. This-
Imagine walking to the best dog beach in
minutes.
I'm not interested in the dog beach.
I'm interested in the property
...
is the best part. This is the best part.
This is the-
Get in there. Get in front of the camera.
You're a good-looking dude.
Tell me what I want to know.
What does my money get me?
The deal you've been waiting for,
and you will not find anything better at-
Okay. This is the kind of content I want,
but think about how we, no offense, we
kind of butchered the beginning of this
... four-bedroom gem in San Marcos
is the deal you've been waiting for, and
you will not find anything better at this
price.
At what price? There you go. 1.24 million.
Again,
I shouldn't have to go to the caption.
This should've been your establishing
shot. This here.
What if I told you you could live in this
house for 1.24
million, and better yet,
it's right next to a dog beach?
But less about that,
let's get back to the property.
I've been rolling on the-
Voiceover. Great choice of song. Spacious.
Interior design. Well-lit. Family home.
Perfect for a young family
... riding
85. I've been thinking way too much
and I'm way
too gone to drive.
The reason this didn't get the views it
deserves is because of how you approach
the
first five seconds.
...
stunning four-bedroom gem in San Marcos
is the deal you've been waiting
for.
I'm excited for you, Josh. I am.
I'm excited. Let me tell you this.
People wanted to know more about
that property.
But we just didn't feed the algorithm what
it needs.
So I want you to take that hook. This
is what this buys you
in this place. That's the hook. Now,
I'm not asking you to steal.
I'm asking you to identify that
is working for a lot of other creators,
and if you can implement
that into your properties...
And do you know what?
They don't even have to be for sale.
I'm going to throw it out there.
If you can find some properties, even
if your mate lives in an amazing house or
someone's like even one of your clients
that you've sold and settled with,
be like,
"Hey, mate.
Do you reckon I could come just show
people your home just so they can
get an understanding of the value of what
a home could get?
And maybe you might even get some offers."
"Hey, bro.
I know your house isn't for sale,
but do you mind if I come just show people
the
property and maybe we'll get a few offers
from it?" You can always say no.
People like to show off.
They might want to show off their
property.
"Hey, bro,
do you mind showing off your property?
Can I come have a little tour?" There's so
much going on here, bro.
So much to go through.
I'm excited for you.
But anyway, so long story short,
Josh actually was in my Discord this
morning and introducing himself.
I was like, "Mate,
I'm so excited about this
that I have to make a video." If you
want to know more about working with me,
there'll be links in the description, and
if you enjoyed this video,
you're probably going to love this one.
But actually,
you might not because this one's got
nothing to do with property.
But you should watch it anyway